store.com 2019-06-30

# CBS Privacy Policy Highlights :: CBS Interactive

Welcome to the network of interactive services provided by CBS Corporation, its affiliates and its subsidiaries (collectively “ **CBS** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **we** ”). CBS is committed to protecting your privacy. CBS is committed to protecting your privacy as further described in the full CBS Privacy Policy. This summary sets out the key points about how CBS handles your personal information.

##### Privacy Policy Scope

CBS owns, operates, or provides access to, several interactive web sites, mobile and connected TV applications, and other interactive features that provide an authorized link to the CBS Privacy Policy (collectively “ **CBS Services** ”). When you use CBS Services, we may collect your personal information in accordance with the CBS Privacy Policy to carry out our activities. The CBS Privacy Policy describes in detail the types of information collected about you when you visit the CBS Services; how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected.

» Read more

##### Information Collected

We collect a variety of information about you, including:

  * Information you provide directly to CBS Services.
  * Information about your computer and browsing activities on the Services, including through cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies.
  * Information about you from other third-party sources , including your personal information if you access a CBS Service through social networking services such as Facebook and Twitter.
  * Information about you from other sources where permitted by law.

» Read more

##### Use of Information

The purpose for which we use the personal information we collect will depend on the particular interaction you have with CBS Services. We use the information we collect to:

  * Provide the services you request.
  * Tell you about offers we think you will value.
  * Customize the content and advertising you see.
  * Improve your experience on CBS Services.
  * And, as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or with your consent.

» Read more

##### Disclosure of Information

We may share your information:

  * Where we have obtained your consent, including with video content and social networking services as described in our Video Services Policy.
  * With our third party service providers.
  * With business partners who sponsor a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion; or who jointly offer a service or feature with a CBS Service.
  * Within the family of [CBS businesses](http://www.cbscorporation.com/our-portfolio).
  * If a CBS Service is sold to another company.
  * To protect or defend the rights of CBS or our users.
  * When required by law or public authorities.

» Read more

##### How to Contact Us

If you have questions regarding the CBS Privacy Policy, please contact us and we will endeavor to respond to your request within a reasonable period of time. You may also submit questions or comments using the postal address listed below:

CBS Interactive Inc. 235 Second Street San Francisco, CA 94105 USA Attn: Legal Department 

We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any privacy concern.

##### California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which a CBS Service has disclosed certain information during the preceding year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us. For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the subject field of your request and include the name of the CBS Services with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we will not accept these requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information. For additional information for residents of the State of California, click here. 

##### EU Data Subject Rights

The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides certain rights for EU data subjects. For additional information for residents of the EU, click here.

##### Canada Privacy Rights

The Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) provides certain rights for Canadian residents. For additional information for residents of Canada, [click here](https://www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy/canada)

##### Australia Privacy Rights

The Australian Privacy Act provides certain rights to Australian residents. For additional information for residents of Australia, [click here](https://www.cbsinteractive.com/legal/cbsi/privacy-policy/australia)
